# Komal Kanaujiya

Indore M.P | 9340880385 | komalfab03@gmail.com

## Websites, Portfolios, Profiles

https://www.linkedin.com/in/komalkanaujiya-16520b146

## Summary

Flexible and focused team player with expertise in customer relationship management, HR proficiencies, Team management. Highly passionate for continuous growth with outstanding outcomes. Holding relevant skills, work experience, qualifications and confident approach that makes me stand out from the crowd.

### Skills

- Salesforce CRM
- Job posting
- Basic computer
- · Team management
- Performance management
- Recruitment
- Cold calling

- · Digital marketing
- Recruitment and Staffing
- Payroll
- Human Resources Operations
- Staff Management
- Employee Onboarding

## Experience

HR GENERAL MANAGER | 07/2023 - Current

360 Digital Printing Innovations - Indore

#### Manufacturing Unit, Sales, Service & Overall staff management

- · Trained employees on duties, policies and procedures.
- Created schedules, monitored attendance, leaves and payroll.
- · Handling recruitments, offer letter, onboarding activities for new hires, exit interviews and ESIC records.

TEAMMATE | 02/2021 - 06/2023

TaskUs - Indore

#### Operations department BPO-US Based

- · Handled team of 10
- Performance management of team (Quality audits and Dsat scrubbing)
- · Constant top performer
- Fintech process customer query handling
- · Got promoted as a Team Leader.

ASSOCIATE | 02/2018 - 06/2019

#### Paytm - SRCOMSOFT - Jabalpur

## Operations department BPO-Domestic

- Ops round Interviews, Selection- 9 months
- Training to new employees- Paytm Money
- Customer support- Mutual Fund/ Recharge
- Data management- KYC
- Performance management of team- 1:1 Sessions
- Constant top performer.

HR EXECUTIVE | 04/2017 - 09/2017

#### Infotek Solutions - Bhopal

#### IT company US Based- HR department

- · Talent acquisition: Recruitment, Initial screening
- Job posting through digital market
- Canva- For Job poster.
- · Cold calling for virtual & walkin interviews.

## **Education and Training**

Shri Ram Institute of Management - MBA HR & Finance

Mata gujri college - B.com